Fans are market manipulating ticket master choose any large tour watch the best section
Ticketmaster makes an additional 650 ms per year by letting their rich broker friends take these tickets before you
Can we build this ourselves sign up for one to three new email accounts?
Find a concert that you want to go to and give your AI agent this prompt
It will scour the internet and sign up for every possible fan club or newsletter or something for your artist that it can find now
Create a workflow like this whenever one of those email accounts gets an email
It sends it to your AI agent to see if it includes any presale codes or information of when the presale will happen
And if so save it to some sort of database now give this next prompt your agent will take that presale code and create a
puppeteer script purchase the seats as soon as they go on presale using one of these payment methods
Technically super illegal by the way, but that hasn't stopped the brokers from using over
6,000 fake accounts to do exactly that don't get screwed by these brokers screw them back with their own method and follow your
Boy while you're at it. I will teach you how to build all of these things for free